{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=",
      "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
      "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
      "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlICJIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIiPw==",
      "correct_answer": "Si5LLiBSb3dsaW5n",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Si5SLlIuIFRvbGtpZW4=",
        "VGVycnkgUHJhdGNoZXR0",
        "RGFuaWVsIFJhZGNsaWZmZQ=="
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=",
      "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
      "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
      "question": "R2VvcmdlIE9yd2VsbCB3cm90ZSB0aGlzIGJvb2ssIHdoaWNoIGlzIG9mdGVuIGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgYSBzdGF0ZW1lbnQgb24gZ292ZXJubWVudCBvdmVyc2lnaHQu",
      "correct_answer": "MTk4NA==",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "VGhlIE9sZCBNYW4gYW5kIHRoZSBTZWE=",
        "Q2F0Y2hlciBhbmQgdGhlIFJ5ZQ==",
        "VG8gS2lsbCBhIE1vY2tpbmdiaXJk"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=",
      "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
      "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
      "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIGJvb2sgaXMgc3ViLXRpdGxlZCAnVGhlIE1vZGVybiBQcm9tZXRoZXVzJz8=",
      "correct_answer": "RnJhbmtlbnN0ZWlu",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "RHJhY3VsYQ==",
        "VGhlIFN0cmFuZ2UgQ2FzZSBvZiBEci4gSmVreWxsIGFuZCBNci4gSHlkZSA=",
        "VGhlIExlZ2VuZCBvZiBTbGVlcHkgSG9sbG93"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=",
      "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
      "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
      "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgQ2FwdGFpbiBOZW1vJ3Mgc3VibWFyaW5lIGluICIyMCwwMDAgTGVhZ3VlcyBVbmRlciB0aGUgU2VhIj8=",
      "correct_answer": "VGhlIE5hdXRpbHVz",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "VGhlIE5lcHR1bmU=",
        "VGhlIFBvc2VpZG9uICA=",
        "VGhlIEF0bGFudGlz"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=",
      "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
      "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
      "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgd29ybGQncyBiZXN0LXNlbGxpbmcgYm9vaz8=",
      "correct_answer": "VGhlIExvcmQgb2YgdGhlIFJpbmdz",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "VGhlIExpdHRsZSBQcmluY2U=",
        "SGFycnkgUG90dGVyIGFuZCB0aGUgUGhpbG9zb3BoZXIncyBTdG9uZQ==",
        "VGhlIERhIFZpbmNpIENvZGU="
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=",
      "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
      "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
      "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBub3ZlbCAnRmVhciBBbmQgTG9hdGhpbmcgSW4gTGFzIFZlZ2FzJz8=",
      "correct_answer": "SHVudGVyIFMuIFRob21wc29u",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ri4gU2NvdHQgRml0emdlcmFsZA==",
        "SGVucnkgTWlsbGVy",
        "V2lsbGlhbSBTLiBCdXJyb3VnaHM="
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=",
      "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
      "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
      "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSB5b3VuZyBhZHVsdCBub3ZlbCAiVGhlIEZhdWx0IGluIE91ciBTdGFycyI/",
      "correct_answer": "Sm9obiBHcmVlbg==",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "U3RlcGhlbmllIE1leWVy",
        "U3V6YW5uZSBDb2xsaW5z",
        "U3RlcGhlbiBDaGJvc2t5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=",
      "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
      "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
      "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgYXV0aG9yIG9mIHRoZSAxOTU0IG5vdmVsLCAiTG9yZCBvZiB0aGUgRmxpZXMiPw==",
      "correct_answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBHb2xkaW5n",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "U3RlcGhlbiBLaW5n",
        "Ri4gU2NvdHQgRml0emdlcmFsZA==",
        "SHVudGVyIEZveA=="
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=",
      "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
      "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
      "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdGhyZWUgaGVhZGVkIGRvZyBpbiBIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIgYW5kIHRoZSBTb3JjZXJlcidzIFN0b25lPw==",
      "correct_answer": "Rmx1ZmZ5",
      "incorrect_answers": ["U3Bpa2U=", "UG9vZnk=", "U3BvdA=="]
    },
    {
      "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=",
      "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
      "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
      "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdGl0bGUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IFNoZXJsb2NrIEhvbG1lcyBib29rIGJ5IEFydGh1ciBDb25hbiBEb3lsZT8=",
      "correct_answer": "QSBTdHVkeSBpbiBTY2FybGV0",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "VGhlIFNpZ24gb2YgdGhlIEZvdXI=",
        "QSBDYXNlIG9mIElkZW50aXR5",
        "VGhlIERvaW5ncyBvZiBSYWZmbGVzIEhhdw=="
      ]
    }
  ]
}
